so how in the world do you actually get
your coaching business to make 10 20
$30,000 a month without being sleazy
slimy or
salesy I don't like any of that and
truthfully I think there's way too much
of it in this industry and it's not
something that I teach people and yet
the businesses that we've built have
been able to make over10 to20 million
per year in profit and so what I want to
talk about with you is if you're just
starting out you want to make 10,000
20,000 $30,000 a month how do you
actually do that without that sleazy
slimy process here's the problem is most
people they end up becoming way too
focused on the money they end up
becoming way too focused on bringing in
the cash flow now I'll say this I think
to have a business you have to make the
cash flow be in your planning your
processes the activities that you do in
your business needs to be most important
you need to do the stuff that actually
brings in the money but in the way that
you do that the way that you communicate
needs to come across authentically to
connect with somebody to solve a problem
for them and what do you truly feel
called to help people with for me I feel
called to help coaches mentors course
creators that are struggling to Market
and grow their businesses and I have a
strategy a system a process that we've
mastered over the last 21 almost 22
years for creating massive amounts of
scale and sales without being sleazy or
slimy and so here's the way that you do
that is you have to do two things number
one you have to address your thinking
you have to address how you think about
your business okay realize that sales
does not equal manipulation and you need
to get out of this fear of rejection or
worry about what other people might
think about you okay so these two things
go double fold I find that often times
what stops people from being successful
is they're way too worried about what
everybody thinks about them and so then
when they come out there to actually
build their business they they are they
don't want to be sleazy they don't want
to be slimy but then they're not showing
up in their authentic self because they
want people to like them they want
people to trust them they want people to
buy from them and and see their value
and all of that's
great but having that be your goal ends
up falling flat and so if you can figure
out who is the person that I help how do
I help them the most and you figure out
exactly what their problems are how do
you figure that out well they will tell
you when you create an opportunity for
them to tell you when you create moments
of conversation where you can listen to
people and they're going to tell you
what are they struggling with and then
you create a product around what people
want here's the thing you might have
some great ideas and things that you
want to share with people but what do
people actually want that's that's what
you need to start selling to people and
figure out what they want people don't
buy what you want them to want they buy
what they want because it they believe
that there's a transformation and a
result that's going to come out of that
and that's where we identify the niche
that we are creating in our business and
then you create an irresistible offer
where you package something in such a
way that it's so good so enticing it
sounds so appealing that it's hard for
people to say no to it that's in the
form of your the way that you package
your content and I'm not talking about
like like the colors or The Branding by
the way when I talk about packaging I'm
talking about the words that you use
words are the packaging of sales words
are the way that we express the value
that people can get from it and so in
our irresistible offer if we can figure
out how to
describe the result that we're offering
and we promise to people to get them
that result people find it nearly
impossible to say no when they are the
right most qualified person and here's
the deal most of the people that you're
going to meet are not qualified for what
you are trying to sell they're not the
right person and that's okay you might
think that anybody who fogs a mirror is
the right person but that's not true
truthful and even if your product could
help everybody you got to realize that
just because it can help somebody
doesn't mean that they're ready for it
and so here's what we got to identify is
who are the people that are actively
looking for what you have to
offer they're actively seeking it out
they're actively seeking that solution
that transformation they're they're
they're willing to do whatever it
takes to solve the problem that your
coaching offer solves that your course
offers solves that's your lead magnet
solves okay and here's the thing those
are actually the only people that are
going to take action with you we live in
a world today where everybody is
inundated with so much
messaging there is social media content
everywhere there's YouTube videos
there's AI that information is
everywhere but the only reason why
people act take action anymore on any
offer that you put out there is because
it is directly in alignment with the
perfect pressing problem that is
festering in their mind that is
bothering them more than anything else
so what you do is you create an offer
around a very specific problem that
somebody
has instead of something that's a me too
product that solves everything for
everybody and you're trying to reach
every everybody I meet a lot of coaches
where they say well I serve a wide range
of people and here's the problem with
that you may be able to help a wide
range of people there's a lot of people
that your program can help but when it
comes to marketing it when it comes to
scaling when it comes to reaching those
10,000 20,000 $30,000 months trying to
help a lot of people is not going to
solve your problem you want to help the
specific
ones who are going to buy from you
they're going to stick with you they're
going to take action with you and
they're going to do the work that's not
everybody that's not everybody and it's
not supposed to be and so the way that
we sell without being salesy is we
identify what is the thing that they
need more than anything else that they
are Desiring more than anything else and
they've already sold themselves on it in
the back of their mind this person is
thinking gosh if somebody came up with
this idea if somebody offered me this if
somebody promised me this and you got to
really understand the psychology of
where people are coming from to do this
you got to understand how they're
thinking how they're looking at your
offer how they're they're receiving it
how they're approaching it how they're
approaching the problem they have and
you got to speak to their inner voice
how are they talking to themselves about
the problem that they don't even know
subconsciously they're dealing with and
that my friends is where you tap right
into not just the pain point but the
deepest desire they have and the person
then says wow okay this this solves the
problem I'm looking
for I'm ready to jump in and not
everybody qualifies for that not
everybody fits into that so in your
marketing you want to make it very
clear who it's for who it's not for you
actually want to repel the wrong people
and this is a good thing because when it
comes to marketing when it comes to the
algorithms on social media when it comes
to advertising when it comes to YouTube
when it comes to content
creation trying to make generalist
content about a lot of different
stuff is the fastest way to fail it's
the fastest way to not get results and I
meet so many coaches and course graders
that do that they're trying to cast a
wide
net worst move you can
make biggest waste of time you can do
and it leads always to the worst
possible outcome and so when you can
figure out very specifically and this
means getting rid of fomo okay getting
rid of the fear of missing out on an
opportunity to help somebody who might
might need what you have to offer become
okay with the fact that there are people
out there that you can help that you're
not going to help I'm going to say it
again you need to become okay with the
fact that there are people out there
that you can
help that you're going to choose to not
make an offer to
help because it will amplify your
ability to help the ones that are meant
to work with you by getting rid of that
whole group of people by culling them
out of your system by literally
strategically aligning yourself away
from people who might need what you have
to offer but because they're not going
to buy from you you don't develop your
offer around them you develop an offer
around the ones who are going to
actually purchase and get results and
this is one of the hardest things that I
see the people do because they they're
afraid of missing out on op
opportunity you can't be afraid of that
and so then when you build an offer
around what people actually
want and you start to create a lead
magnet you start to grow your email
list and then with that you can sell to
them something that solves their problem
what are you selling something that is
the solution to the
thing that they are looking for for we
take the niche of what they want their
desire you package it up into something
that solves their problem and then you
find as many people as possible that are
out there on the internet that need that
and how do we find those people we
create content we create trainings we
create opportunities for
conversations and we promise here's the
key we promise to be able to solve the
problem for somebody now you can't
guarantee that they're going to get the
problem solved but you can guarantee
that you have a path to get them there
if they start to take action and follow
through on the things that you're
selling and then what your job is is to
amplify that promise
that desire fulfilled that wish
fulfilled they have a wish they have a
dream they have something they want and
and you are the answer to that wish for
my clients I am the answer to the thing
that they have been dreaming about most
that somebody would come along with a
proven process a proven system that they
don't have to work more than 10 hours a
week so that they can even do it while
they're working at another job so that
they actually start to get results so
they don't have to burn a ton of money
on advertising and can actually make the
kind of money that they want to make in
their business that's what our coaching
program does that's what my client
growth accelerator program does below
there's actually a training that you can
watch on how we do this and how that
process works I'd love to invite you to
go check that out I think it will really
help you to get results in your business
and to be able to take it to the next
level for you to have consistent income
for you to have clarity as to how you
design your offer and your messaging and
so that you can have the financial and
time Freedom that you want that's what I
love and live
for is seeing people being able to
experience their dreams experience their
dream business experience their dream
life that's what I've seen happen with
hundreds of coaches that I've worked
with over the years I've helped
thousands of people get started and
hundreds of people reach seven figure
status and I can help you as well and
I'd love to do that in my client growth
accelerator program that's my Premier
coaching program where I work with you
through every single day how to grow
your business build your offers create
your landing pages create your sales
copy your ads how to do the sales
process how to sell to people what are
the words strategically to say that are
going to get people to buy from you and
more that's what we cover in there and
it's not about being sleazy it's not
about being slimy it's about learning
how to make a connection with people
that really need what you have to offer
and you just find those people you find
who are those
people they have a problem that you can
solve and you can create systems that
actually find those people you can use
artificial intelligence to help you
develop ideas for your marketing to help
you brainstorm the best ways to Market
and communicate with those people all of
my content all of the ideas that I do
even this video right here was an idea
that I got using our AI strategies that
we
teach and I can show you how to do that
as well in my accelerator program I'd
love to see you in there and I'd love to
work with you on that make sure you
subscribe make sure you follow our
videos we got thousands of videos here
on this
page and it's time for you to start
getting results in your business and
making the kind of money that you can
make I believe you can do it in fact I
know you can you just got to take action
you got to get off your your seat you
got to get off your hands and you got to
start doing the work and start reaping
the rewards I'd love to help you get
there we'll talk to soon everybody have
a good one